[
  {
    "Type" : "Multiple",
    "Question": "Count the <b>vowel clusters</b>: \"This summer I am going on a cruise ship.\"",
    "Options": ["1", "5", "3", "2"],
    "Answer": "2",
    "ID": "x1"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Multiple",
    "Question": "Count the <b>consonant clusters</b>: \"My cats are always fighting each other.\"",
    "Options": ["5", "1", "0", "4"],
    "Answer": "4",
    "ID": "x2"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Multiple",
    "Question": "How many vowels does the word \"Machine\" contain?",
    "Options": ["2", "3", "1", "4"],
    "Answer": "3",
    "ID": "x3"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Match",
    "Question": "Re-order the words in alphabetical order.",
    "Options": ["Xylophone", "Journal", "Yellow", "Dog", "Scene"],
    "Answer": "Dog journal scene xylophone yellow",
    "ID": "x4"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Multiple",
    "Question": "Come si dice \"Saluto\"?",
    "Options": ["Great", "Grape", "Greeting", "Stew"],
    "Answer": "Greeting",
    "ID": "x5"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Match",
    "Question": "Riordina le lettere per ottenere la parola \"Nutrire\" in inglese.",
    "Options": ["s", "i", "h", "o", "u", "n", "r"],
    "Answer": "N o u r i s h",
    "ID": "x6"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Multiple",
    "Question": "Come si dice \"Meteo\" (o \"Clima\")?",
    "Options": ["Zealous", "Umbrella", "Where", "Weather"],
    "Answer": "Weather",
    "ID": "x7"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Fill",
    "Question": "Inserisci le parole corrette negli spazi vuoti.",
    "Problem": "I like [INSERT]ead, it's delici[INSERT]s",
    "Options": ["CR", "BR", "TR", "AU", "OU"],
    "Answer": "I like bread, it's delicious",
    "ID": "x8"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Multiple",
    "Question": "When is \"y\" considered a vowel?",
    "Options": ["At the end of a sentence", "At the end of a word", "At the end of a word and syllable", "After a consonant", "Never"],
    "Answer": "At the end of a word and syllable",
    "ID": "x9"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Fill",
    "Question": "Inserisci le parole corrette negli spazi vuoti.",
    "Problem": "The [INSERT] is sunny. We don't need an [INSERT].",
    "Options": ["Warm", "Dry", "Weather", "Cold", "Umbrella", "Rain"],
    "Answer": "The weather is sunny. We don't need an umbrella.",
    "ID": "x10"
  },
  {
    "Type" : "Fill",
    "Question": "Inserisci le parole corrette negli spazi vuoti.",
    "Problem": "I would like to get the [INSERT] cutlet and a bottle of [INSERT].",
    "Options": ["Pink", "Thin", "Water", "British", "Pork", "Rooster"],
    "Answer": "I would like to get the pork cutlet and a bottle of water.",
    "ID": "x11"
  }
]
